http://www.ventanawild.org/privacy-policy

HomeTrailsExplore the TrailsVentana Wilderness TrailsSilver Peak Wilderness TrailsState Parks TrailsSupport the TrailsStewardshipTrail ProgramVolunteer Wilderness RangersArchaeological Site StewardshipMarijuana Grow Site CleanupsSuccess Story: Willow Creek RestorationYouth in WildernessProgram OverviewYiW TeamYiW OutingsSHE HIKESLeadership InitiativesBecome a YiW PartnerBecome a YiW FunderAdvocacyAccomplishmentsWildfire PlanningMilpitas Special Interest AreaFort Hunter LiggettNEPA & CEQAGrazingPlan a TripTrip SuggestionsMaps & BooksWeather, Road & Trail ConditionsLeave No Trace!Sykes Camp / Sykes Hot SpringsArroyo Seco – Keep it WildAboutMission & PurposeWho We AreNewsletterContact UsAbout the LandNatural ResourcesCultural ResourcesDouble Cone Register Natural History JournalLost & Invisible CampsMaps & BooksForumsSupport UsJoin/ Renew/ DonateLegacy Giving2020 Film Festival
Privacy
Donate!
HomeTrailsExplore the TrailsVentana Wilderness TrailsSilver Peak Wilderness TrailsState Parks TrailsSupport the TrailsStewardshipTrail ProgramVolunteer Wilderness RangersArchaeological Site StewardshipMarijuana Grow Site CleanupsSuccess Story: Willow Creek RestorationYouth in WildernessProgram OverviewYiW TeamYiW OutingsSHE HIKESLeadership InitiativesBecome a YiW PartnerBecome a YiW FunderAdvocacyAccomplishmentsWildfire PlanningMilpitas Special Interest AreaFort Hunter LiggettNEPA & CEQAGrazingPlan a TripTrip SuggestionsMaps & BooksWeather, Road & Trail ConditionsLeave No Trace!Sykes Camp / Sykes Hot SpringsArroyo Seco – Keep it WildAboutMission & PurposeWho We AreNewsletterContact UsAbout the LandNatural ResourcesCultural ResourcesDouble Cone Register Natural History JournalLost & Invisible CampsMaps & BooksForumsSupport UsJoin/ Renew/ DonateLegacy Giving2020 Film Festival
Search ...
Find
Privacy Policy
Effective April 9, 2015
Privacy Notice Table of Contents
Our Commitment To Privacy
The Information We Collect
How We Use Information
Our Commitment To Data Security
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
How To Access Or Correct Your Information
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the www.ventanawild,org website. On some pages, you can make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you request information online and want it sent directly to another party, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an information request only to complete that request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that request. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing a request only to fulfill that request and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that request.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing a request to . You will be contacted within 48 hours using the phone number we have on file. Once confirmed your file will be delivered via the method of your choice. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (831) 423-3191 or send us an email at .
Copyright © 1999-2020 Ventana Wilderness Alliance.
Website By: Tree Top Web Design
PrivacyTermsSitemapVWA CalendarContact
Desktop Version
